Preliminary Inventory to the Carla A. Hills Papers, 1964-1993
Hoover Institution Archives
- Chron - CAH -, June, 1974
- Chron - CAH -, May, 1974
- Chron - CAH -, April, 1974
- Telephone Sheets, April - December, 1974
- CAH - Congratulatory Letters re Appointment as Assistant Attorney General, Civil Division
- White House News Conference - #196 to #258, (1975) (Box 104)
- White House News Conference - #259 to #311, (1975)
- White House News Conference - #312 to #363, (1975)
- White House News Conference - #364 to #404, (1975)
- White House News Conference - #406 to #448, (1975) (Box 105)
- White House News Conference - #449 to #486, (1975) (March - April)
- White House News Conference - #487 to #524, (1976) (May - June)
- White House News Conference - #525 to #572, (1976) (July - August)
- White House News Conference #573 to #596, (1976) (September - October) (Box 106)
- CHRISTMAS CARDS
  - Christmas, 1975
  - Original List
- OPERATING SUBSIDIES FOR PUBLIC HOUSING -- Performance Funding
- PUERTO RICO -- Inauguration --, 1/2/77
- MASONRY INDUSTRY
- TRAVEL
  - CAH/HUD, FY 76 -
  - CAH/HUD, FY 75 -
  - CAH/HUD, FY 74 -
  - Department of Justice, (1974)
- TAPE CASSETTES from CAH (Box 107)
  - Swearing-in Ceremony, Department of Justice, 4/1/74
  - Swearing-in Ceremony, HUD, 3/10/75; (2 tapes)
  - Brooklyn College Speech by Jimmy Carter -, 9/7/76
  - City Club of Cleveland -, 10/6/76
  - Speech and Qs and As, Dallas, Texas -, 10/13/76
  - Meeting w/Minority Group in Dallas -, 10/13/76
  - Dallas News Interview, Part 1 -, 10/13/76
  - Dallas News Interview, Part 2 -, 10/13/76
  - Akron Public Affairs Forum Speech/Press Conference, 10/14/76
  - California League of Cities, Senator Mondale Speech, 10/19/76
  - California League of Cities, CAH Speech, 10/19/76
  - Commonwealth Club of San Francisco, CAH Speech/Qs and As, 10/20/76
  - Hills/Coleman Joint Press Conference, San Francisco-, 10/20/76
  - Stanford Daily Press Interview, San Francisco -, 10/20/76
  - Florida Home Builders Reception, Orlando, Florida -, 10/28/76
  - Oakwood-Villa Project Remarks to Press, Jacksonville-, 10/29/76
  - Florida Times Union Interview, Jacksonville, Florida-, 10/29/76
  - Mortgage Bankers Association, San Francisco -, 10/27/76
  - Detroit Economic Club Speech/Qs and As, 11/1/76
  - Detroit Economic Club, Press Availability -, 11/1/76
  - Business Outlook Conference, Los Angeles -, 11/18/76
  - NAHRO, Session 8, Tape 2
  - Unidentified Tape
- MASSACHUSETTS HOUSING FINANCE AGENCY Study Commission Report, 6/1976
- CONGRESSIONAL HEARINGS by Carla A. Hills
- CODE OF FEDERAL REGULATIONS
  - CFR - Parts 0 to 499, Revised as of, 24, 1976 4/1/76
  - CFR - Parts 500 to End, Revised as of, 24, 1976 4/1/76
- CITY OF DETROIT, Map, HUD-ACQUIRED SINGLE-FAMILY PROPERTIES, 3/3/75
- Median Value of Owner Occupied Housing Units by Counties of the United States:, 1970
- Median Gross Rent by Counties of the United States:, 1970
- Justice (Box 108)
  - Accounting/Auditing Act of -- S.2049, 1973
  - Adams v. Weinberger (Dummy File)
  - Administrative Matters
  - Admiralty and Shipping (Miscellaneous Matters)
  - Advocacy Training (Dummy File)
  - Affidavits
  - Agenda Items re Civil Division - Staff Meetings
  - Agenda for Briefing Conferences
  - Agency Clients
  - Agency Conflicts
  - Agency Litigating Authority
  - Agency Press Releases/Other Official Public Statements
    Re: Pending Litigation Proposed Order Requiring J/D Clearance
  - Agency Special Interest Cases "Red Circle"
    - Baker, Charles and Charlene, et al. v. F&F Investment Company, et al. and FHA, et al. C.A. 7 No. 72-2036
    - Barrett, et al. v. CSC and NASA "Red Circle"
    - Hale, Francis v. HUD "Red Circle"
    - NWRO v. HEW, USDC, D. D.C. Civil Action No. 264-73 "Red Circle"
    - WEAL, et al. v. Weinberger, et al., USDC, D. D.C., Civil No. 74-1720 "Red Circle"
    - Agency Special Interest Cases "Red Circle"
  - Agriculture
  - Air Freight Procedures
  - Allison, Kenneth, et al. v. Secretary of the Navy, et al. (Dummy File)
  - American Society for Public Administration, Annual Conference -, 11/14-15/74
  - Amnesty
  - Annual Productivity Report Briefing
  - Annual Report by D/J, 1974
  - Application of Merit Principles to Personnel Actions within D/J
  - Attorneys Fees Awards Against U.S.
  - Attorney General's Briefing Book
  - Attorney General's First Trial Advocacy Institute
    - Attorney General's First Trial Advocacy Institute
    - White v. United States, et al.
  - Second Trial Advocacy Sessions AG's Advocacy Institute
  - Attorney General's Senior Executive Seminars
  - Authorization to Pay Attorney's Fees in Social Security Cases Following Court Order of Such Fees
  - Automated Retrieval System Committee, Civil Division (CDARSC)
  - Awards
    - Federal Woman's Award
    - Justice Tom C. Clark Award
    - Civil Division Special Award
    - Awards - Special Achievements
    - AG's Annual Award Ceremony
    - Awards - Special Commendation
    - Awards - Miscellaneous
    - Awards - Seniority
  - Axelrad, Nancy
  - Bailey, Shirley, et al. v. Mandel, Marvin, et al., USDC, D. Md. Civil Action No. K-74-1102 (Box 109)
  - Bernardi, Jean C., et al. v. Butz, Earl L., Secretary of Agriculture, CA 9 No. 74-2180
  - Black Lung Litigation
  - Board of Parole
  - Bradley, Tom, et al. v. Saxbe, William, USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1327
  - Briefing of Deputy
  - Briefing on Civil Division
  - Buckley, James L., et al. v. Valeo, Hon. Francis R., et al., USDC, D. D.C. Civil No. 75-0001
    - Buckley, et al. v. Valeo, et al., USDC, D. D.C. Civil No. 75-0001 CORRESPONDENCE
    - Buckley, et al. v. Valeo, et al., USDC, D. D.C. Civil No. 75-0001 PLEADINGS
    - Buckley, et al. v. Valeo, et al., U.S. Court of Appeals, D.C. Cir. No. 75-1061 PLEADINGS
  - Budget - FY-74
  - Budget - FY-75
  - Budget - FY-76
  - FY-77 Program Activity Structure
  - Canal National Bank, et al. v. Peter Mills, et al., USDC, D. Maine No. 74-82-S.D.
  - Central Files (Maintenance)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA)
  - Centralized Statistical Capabilities for the Department of Justice
  - Civil Division
    - Description of Civil Division
    - Reorganization of Civil Division
    - Organization Chart of Civil Division
  - Civil Division Internal Memos
  - Civil Division Manual
  - Civil Division (Move)
  - GSA-CSC
    - Civil Service Commission Legislation
    - Corneal v. Hampton/Roush v. Hampton
    - GSA v. CSC Pleadings
    - Civil Service Commission (CSC) Jurisdiction to Discipline for Violation re Merit System
  - Claims for Civil Money Penalties
  - Clemency Board
  - Clerical Personnel Matters
  - COINTELPRO
  - Collection Matters
    - Collections Conference, 1975
    - Collection of Debts Due U.S. by Offset Against Refunds Payable by IRS to Individual Taxpayers
    - Collection of Judgments from Other Division
    - Statistics on Money Due U.S.
    - Collections and Judgments
  - Committee on the Office of A/G
  - Consultants
  - Consumers Union of the U.S. v. William B. Saxbe
  - Contract Disputes Act of, 1975
  - Corporation Source Book Statistics of Income
  - Court of Appeals - Reorganization
  - Court of Claims Miscellaneous Matters
  - Criminal Justice Information Control and Protection of Privacy Act of, 1974
  - Criminal Trial Training Program
  - Decentralization of D/J Correspondence Management System (Box 110)
  - Department of Defense Petroleum Allocation
  - Defense Matters
    - Defense
    - Inalouise Cates, et al. v. L.T.V. Aerospace Corp., et al.
    - Parker, Jacob J. Warden, et al. v. Levy, Howard B. No. 73-206 Supreme Court Appeal from U.S. Court of [UNK] 3d Circuit
  - Diggs, Charles Coles, Jr., et al. v. Dent, Frederick B., USDC, D. D.C., Civil No. 74-1292
  - Directory - General Counsels
  - DuPree, Daniel Gonzales, Consul of Mexico v. USA, USDC, S.D. Cal, Civil No. 73-39-GT
  - Economic Stabilization
  - Employment of Handicapped
  - Encroachments on Litigating Authority of Attorney General
  - Exclusionary Rule
  - Expenses from Luncheons, etc.
  - Explosion Cases from California and Nevada
  - Federal Bar Association 1974 Convention, September 3-7, 1974
  - Federal Claims Collection Act of, 1966
  - Federal Communications Commission
  - FCC-U.S. Attorneys
  - FCC (Re: Pacifica Station) 47 U.S.C. 503 (b) (1) (E)
  - Federal Executive Development Program
  - Federal Instrument Act of (S. 3514), 1973
  - Federal Reformatory for Women Visiting Committee (White House Inquiry)
  - Federal Trade Commission Act Legislation
  - Federal Woman's Program (Equal Employment Opportunity for Women)
  - Financial Interest of Staff
  - Fitzgerald (Dummy File)
  - Florida East Coast Railway Co. v. United States, U.S. Court of Claims No. 532-69
    - Correspondence
    - Pleadings
  - Food Stamps v. Butz
  - Foreign Litigation Miscellaneous Matters
  - Foreign Sovereign Immunity Draft Bill
  - Foreign Visitor to D/J
  - Frauds Miscellaneous Matters
  - Freedom of Information Act
  - Gaballah, Saeed v. Johnson, Donald, USDC, N.D. Ill., No. 72-C-1973
  - Garnishments Against U.S. Pursuant to Public Law 93-647
  - Gateway Center Corporation; John W. Merriam v. Sampson, Arthur F., USDC, E.D. Pa., Civil No. 71-2262
  - Letters from General Counsel
  - General Claims Section Miscellaneous
  - General Litigation Miscellaneous Matters
  - General Litigation Work Load
  - Greenfield, Greg, et al. v. Harker, Dennis, et al., USDC, S.D. Iowa, Civil No. 74-114-1
  - Griffin, Richard J. and Mary Jane v. USA (Dummy File)
  - Harrington, Michael J. v. Colby, Kissinger and Simon, USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1884
  - HAU, Jane and Martin v. Secretary of HEW
  - HEW re Legal Requirements for Hrg. u/42 U.S.C. Section 1316 After Denial of Social Services Amendments
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW)
  - HEW - Procedural Defenses
  - Hispanic Activity during FY, 1974
  - Honors Program, (1974)
  - Hughes, Leroy B. v. U.S., USDC, S.D. Texas No. 73-H-556
  - IBM Case (Dummy File) (Box 111)
  - Governor of Idaho v. Agriculture
  - Impoundment
  - Inflation Impact Statements
  - Inter-division Coordination
  - Interior v. Parks Reservation System
  - Interior Power Rate Cases
  - Internal Audit of Debt Collection Activities in Legal Division and U.S. Attorneys Offices
  - Joint Bidding at Outer Continental Shelf Lease Sales
  - Jobs for Veterans Report
  - Jurisdiction of Civil Division
  - Labor Matters
    - MESA-OSHA Mine Enforcement Safety Administration Occupational Safety/Health Administration
    - H.R. 2 (Labor Pension Bill)
    - Wage and Hour cases (Labor)
    - Brennan v. Santa Fe Trail Transportation Co. and Occupational Safety and Health Commission, No. 74-1049, C.A. 10
    - Secretary of Labor v. Chicago Bridge & Iron Co. and Occupational Safety and Health Commission, No. 74-1214, C.A. 7
    - Department of Labor re Litigating Authority Memorandum of Understanding
  - Land and Natural Resources Journal - Department of Justice
  - Legal Aid Society of Alameda County v. Brennan, USDC, N.D. Calif., Civil No. C-73-0282-AJZ
  - Legal Divisions/U.S. Attorneys Relationship, D/J Study
  - Legislation (Pending)
  - Legislative Program, 94th Congress, 1st Session
    - Legislative Program, 94th Congress, 1st Session
    - Legislative Proposals by Civil Division Section/Unit Chiefs
  - Legislative Proposals for Transition to Fiscal Year, 10/1-9/30
  - Librarian
  - Library Bulletin Department of Justice
  - Library Memos
  - Litigation Experience in Civil Division Assessed on Quarterly Basis
  - Litigation Management Study Questionnaire
  - Magidow, Aaron, et al. v. Butz, Earl, et al., USDC, C.D. Cal., Civil No. CV 74-1553-LTL (Box 112)
  - Magistrates
  - Management by Objectives
  - John Marshall Awards Review Panel Nominations, 1974
  - Massachusetts v. Simon, et al.; Algonquin Sng, Inc. v. Simon, et al., USDC, D. D.C. #75-0129; #75-0130 (CONSOLIDATED)
    - Correspondence
    - Pleadings
  - Massachusetts v. Simon, et al.; Algonquin Sng, Inc. v. Simon, et al. USDC, D. D.C. #75-0129; #75-0130
    - PLEADINGS re Massachusetts, et al. v. Simon, et al. USDC, D. D.C. No. 75-0129
    - PLEASINGS re Algonquin Sng, Inc., et al. v. Simon, et al. USDC, D. D.C. No. 75-0130
  - Medicare Overpayment Claims
  - Memoranda Department of Justice
  - Memorandum to AG and DAG
  - Miscellaneous
  - McCord, James W., Jr. v. Ford, Gerald, et al. (TRO) USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1386
  - Nader, Ralph v. Butz
  - Nader, Moss, Abzug & Waldie v. Saxbe, USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1260
    - Pleadings
    - Extra Pleadings
  - National Customs Service Assn. v. Simon, William E., et al., USDC, D.C. No. 74-1127
  - National League of Cities, et al. v. Peter J. Brennan, Supreme Court No. S-553
  - National Welfare Rights Organization v. Casper Weinberger
  - Ninth Judicial Circuit Conference, Reno, Nevada -, 7/29-8/2/74
  - Non-Judicial Foreclosures
  - Occupational Safety and Health Review Committee Litigation, Control Thereof (Box 113)
  - Offer and Compromise for Section Chief
  - Office Machines
    - Dictating Equipment
    - MTST/Video Tape Facilities
    - Mag Card 1 Inter-communication System, Pilot Project at Selected USA Offices
  - Office of Legal Counsel Rulings
  - OPIC Matters
  - Palmer, James F. v. United States Marshal Service
  - Para-Legal Project
  - Pasco Terminals, Inc. v. US; Azufrera Pan Americana, S.A. v. US, Customs Court
  - Patents and Antitrust Laws
  - Patent Legislation - Section 298 of S.2504
  - Patent Licensing Shiley Laboratories v. Weinberger; Public Citizen v. Sampson
  - Phelps v. Saxbe, et al. (Snead) [Dummy File]
  - Postal Service
  - Powell, Dollie M. v. US Govt, USDC, E.D. La. No. 74-3248, Section b
  - Presidential Documents
  - FY 75 Presidential Objectives -- Organized/White Collar Crimes
  - Press Procedures
  - Prisoner Litigation (Sensitive Issue)
  - Private Collection of Judgments (Dummy File)
  - Productivity Workshop on Internal Government Training Efficiency and Effectiveness, 12/4/74
  - Proposed Revision of Court of Claims' Requirements for Printing and Copies
  - Public Information Act Litigation
  - Quality Control Regulations -- Aid to Families with Dependent [UNK]
  - Railroad Reorganization (Dummy File)
  - Renegotiation Board
  - Reorganization of Department of Justice
  - Review of Advisory Committees
  - Roadway Inns of America Inc./Madesco Investment Corp., et al. v. Maurice B. Frank, Ocean Seabreeze Inc., Gen'l Ptrns, Manison House Motor Hotel Company, et al.
  - Santa Barbara Oil Spill (Box 114)
  - Schedule of Department Activities
  - Social Security Benefit Cases
  - Social Security Cases (Appeal/Administration of)
  - Social Security Litigation
  - General SSA Litigation - Change in Printing Transcript
  - Social Security "Roll Back" Cases
    ("SSI" Supplemental Security Income Program)
  - Social Services Cases
  - Special Review Office
  - Speech Materials
    (Trial Advocacy/Specialization/Legal Ethics/Professional Responsibility
  - Standards of Conduct (Enforcement of Departmental)
  - U.S. v. State of California and James Coan (TECA Nos. 9-13/9-14)
  - Statements/Testimony/Speeches (Miscellaneous) Department of Justice
  - State of the Union Message
  - States v. Gerald R. Ford - Oil Import Charge
  - Status of Funds Report (Civil)
  - Stretch, William A., et al. v. Weinberger, Casper W., Secretary of HEW and related cases
  - Study Method/Procedures for Implementing Uniform Law Providing Liability for Clean Up Costs/Damages from Oil Spills from Outer Continental Shelf Operations, etc.
  - Summer Law Clerk Seminar Program - - 4:00 p.m., July 24, 1974
  - Supergrades
  - Supreme Court
  - Supreme Court Hearing List
  - Tariff Commission Matters (Box 115)
    - Tariff Commission (Doxycycling) Pfizer v. Internat'l Rectifier and USV Pharmaceutical, No. 337-L-60
    - Tariff Commission (Ampicillin) Biocraft Laboratories, Inc. v. Bristol Myers, et al., Misc. 45-70
    - State of North Carolina v. Charles Pfizer & Co., Inc., et al. USDC, E.D.N.C. Raleigh Div. No. 2287
    - Tariff Commission - Trade Bill
  - Tariff Commission Matters
    - Tariff Commission (Guidelines)
    - Tariff Commission CORRESPONDENCE
      (Pfizer v. Internat'l Rectifier, CA 8, No. 74-1425)
    - Tariff Commission PLEADINGS
    - Tariff Commission EXTRAS/DRAFTS
  - PFIZER (Dummy File)
  - In Re COORDINATED PRETRAIL PROCEEDINGS IN ANTIBIOTIC ANTITRUST ACTIONS
    United States of America vs. Pfizer, Inc., et al., USDC, D. Minn. #4-71 Civil. 435/#4-71 Civ. 403
  - Talking Points for A.G. Saxbe - Meeting with Departmental General Counsels, April 24, 1974 (Box 116)
  - Tax Division Files re Access
  - TEXACO - FEA
    - Texaco-FEA
    - Texaco v. FEA, USDC, D.Delaware, Civil Action No. 74-234 PLEADINGS
    - Texaco v. FEA, USDC, D.Delaware, Civil Action No. 74-244 PLEADINGS
    - Texaco-FEA - DRAFT/EXTRA COPIES
  - Thobaben, Robert G., Associate Professor, Wright State University, Dayton, Ohio Re: "Attorneys General of the United States: A Role Analysis"
  - Thompson, Charles Dennis v. U.S. Department of Justice, Bureau of Narcotics/Dangerous Drugs, CA 9, No. 74-1847
  - Title 18, USC - Committee Print of a Bill to Codify and Reform
  - Torts Section - Miscellaneous
  - Travel re Civil Division Attorneys
  - Treasury and Customs Duties
  - Trial Participation by Civil Division Attorneys
  - Union Oil Company of California v. Federal Energy Administration (Dummy File)
  - Joint U.S. Attorneys-Civil Division Committee
  - U.S. Attorneys-Civil Chiefs
  - United States Attorneys Advisory Committee: Letters from USAs re letter to Dean Smith and Agency Litigation Reports, 7/19/74
  - U.S. Attorneys Responses to Appeal Policy Letter re "Special Significance Cases"
  - U.S. Attorneys Evaluation of D.C. Office, 1/75
  - Allocation of Work between USAs and Civil Division
  - United States Attorneys
    - Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys -- Agency Complaints re U.S. Attorneys
    - Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys -- Requests by U.S. Attorneys for Civil Division to Handle Litigation
    - Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys -- Relationship between Civil Division and U.S. Attorneys
    - Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys -- U.S. Attorneys' Manual
    - Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys -- Evaluation of U.S. Attorneys Offices
    - Meetings with Individual U.S. Attorneys
    - U.S. Attorneys -- Miscellaneous
  - Advisory Committees of U.S. Attorneys -- Correspondence w/Dean Smith
  - Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys -- Comments from Civil Division on Letters to Dean Smith
  - United States Attorneys
    - United States Attorneys Conference, New Orleans, October 15-19, 1974
    - U.S. Attorneys Conference -- Recommendations from USAs
    - U.S. Attorneys Advisory Committee June Meetings and Report
    - Civil Division/USAs Committee Agenda
  - U.S. Attorneys Bulletin
  - U.S. v. Norfolk Shipbuilding & Drydock Corp., et al., USDC, E.D. Va. Civil No. 74-384-N
  - U.S. Government Manual
  - Ven-Fuel -- FEA (Box 117)
  - Veterans, Estate of -- Claims of U.S. per 38 USC, Section 5520
  - Vietnam Veterans
  - Vocational Rehabilitation Act -- Pocket Veto
  - Weekly Reports to AG
  - Year-end Departmental Report, 1974
  - Yoshida International, Inc. (Dummy File)
  - Zelmanowitz, Gerald, et al., v. United States, USDC, N.D. Cal. Civil No. C-74-1132-SW
  - Zenith Radio Corp. v. Matsushita Electric Industrial Co., Ltd., et al. USDC, E.D. Pa., Civil No. 74-2451
    - Zenith Radio Corp. v. Matsushita Electric Industrial Co., Ltd., et al., USDC, E.D. Pa., Civil No. 74-245
    - Zenith v. Matsushita; National Union v. Matsushita; In Re Japanese Electronic Products -- DRAFTS
    - Zenith v. Matsushita; National Union v. Matsushita; In Re Japanese Electronic Products -- PLEADINGS
  - CONSTITUTIONAL IMMUNITY OF MEMBERS OF CONGRESS, Hearings before the JOINT COMMITTEE ON CONGRESSIONAL OPERATIONS, Congress of the United States, 93rd Congress, 1st Session on "The Legislative Role of Congress in Gathering and Disclosing Information" -, 3/21/73; 3/27-28/73 (Box 118)
  - LIFE INSURANCE Fact Book, 1974
  - FEDERAL PRISON SYSTEM Facilities, 1974
  - EMPLOYMENT FACT BOOK, United States Department of Justice, Office of Management & Finance, Personnel and Training Staff, Systems Planning and Evaluation Group
  - ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICE OF THE UNITED STATES COURTS
    - Opinion of the Honorable Raymond J. Pettine, Chief Judge, United States District Court for the District of Rhode Island, DeCosta v. Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., Civil Action No. 3130, filed, September 23, 1974
    - Listing of Black Lung Cases filed in U.S. District Courts, July, August and September 1974
    - October 1974 issue of "The Third Branch", Vol. 6, No. 10
    - MANAGEMENT STATISTICS for United States Courts, 1974
  - HUD (Department of Housing and Urban Development)
    Reference materials re Appointment as HUD Secretary
  - SUPREME COURT OF THE UNITED STATES
    - Baker, et al., Trustees in Reorganization v.
      Gold Seal Liquors, Inc., No. 73-804
    - Baldridge, et al. v.
      John R. Hadley, et al. and United States of America, No. 73-136
    - Bangor Punta Operations, Inc., et al. v.
      Bangor & Aroostook Railroad Co., et al., No. 73-718
    - Brennan, Peter J., Secretary of Labor v.
      Bachowski, Walter, No. 74-466
    - Butterfield, Alexander P., Administrator of the Federal Aviation Administration, et al., v. Robertson, III, Reuben B and Simandle, Jerome B., No. 74-450
    - Cardwell v. Lewis, No. 72-1603
    - Central Tablet Manufacturing Co. v.
      United States, No. 73-593
    - Codispoti, et al. v. Pennsylvania, No. 73-5615
    - Commissioner of Internal Revenue v.
      Idaho Power Co., No. 73-263
    - Davis v. United States, No. 72-1454
    - Dorszynski v. United States, No. 73-5284
    - Federal Power Commission v.
      Texaco, Inc., et al., No. 72-1490
    - Florida Power & Light Co. v.
      International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 641, et al., No. 73-556
    - Geduldig, Director, Department of Human Resources Developmen v. Aiello, et al., No. 73-640
    - Gertz v. Robert Welch, Inc., No. 72-617
    - Gilmore, et al. v.
      City of Montgomery, Alabama, et al., No. 72-1517
    - Hamling, et al. v. United States, No. 73-507
    - Hampton, Chairman of the Civil Service Commission, et al. v.
      Mow Sun Wong, et al., No. 73-1596
    - Jenkins v. Georgia, No. 73-557
    - Jimenez, et al. v.
      Weinberger, Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare, No. 72-6609
    - Kokoszka v.
      Belford, Trustee in Bankruptcy, No. 73-5265
    - Lehman v. City of Shaker Heights, et al., No. 73-328
    - Lewisburg Penitentiary (Warden) v. Marrero, No. 73-831
    - Miami Herald Publishing Co., Division of Knight Newspapers, Inc. v.
      Tornillo, No. 73-797
    - Michigan v. Tucker, No. 73-482
    - Morton, Secretary of the Interior, et al. v.
      Mancari, et al., No. 73-362
    - Old Dominion Branch No. 496, National Association of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO, et al. v. Austin, et al., No. 72-1180
    - Parker (Warden), et al. v. Levy, No. 73-206
    - Pell, et al. v.
      Procunier, Corrections Director, et al., No. 73-918
    - Place, Diane M. v. Weinberger, Caspar W., Secretary of Health, Education and Welfare, et al., No. 74-116
    - The Renegotiation Board v. Grumman Aircraft Engineering Corporation, No. 73-1316
    - Richardson, County Clerk and Registrar of Voters of Mendoci County v. Ramirez, et al., No. 72-1589
    - Saxbe, Attorney General, et al. v.
      Washington Post Co., et al., No. 73-1265
    - Scherk v. Alberto-Culver Co., No. 73-781
    - Schlesinger, Secretary of Defense, et al. v.
      Reservisits Committee to Stop the War, et al., No. 72-1188
    - Secretary of the Navy v. Mark Avrech, No. 72-1713
    - Spence (Harold Omand) v. State of Washington, No. 72-1690
    - STAATS, Comptroller-General of the United States, General Accounting Office, et al. v. American Civil Liberties Union Inc., et al., No. 73-1413